are your life
what else copies
we're gonna make this terrible laughter
turn
we're here on the Honda Accord testing
out open pilot 0.5
we're going to be releasing this to
devil when the press embargo finishes
well this car so much nice and the Civic
oh so much nicer guys by an a chord
that's great I'm ravenous excited
driving is excited is 0.5 oh do you need
that uncas driver monitoring or just to
see the Scott just to see the struggles
also discoveries can see you
this trip
now Ronnie got 35 cookies yeah they so
fast
it's supposed to be don't we why does it
say that football get them when I press
the brakes yeah autopost on foot
pretty nice
hope I'll zero to five guys check it out
the court actuators are worse than Civic
I fink are slightly better just still
that that amount of torque is about the
same unless you have the secret Civic
Torquemada of course then you get 2x the
Civic torque for real this time guys
we need a court or c'mon yeah we
they won't make a quick talk to talk
about
and sunny for users of this secret good
first enough I see your secret good
civic parameters now we've we fixed up
all the parameters for all the cars what
sound like beeping this car like trying
to tell me something it's probably too
posh this time transit are not always
the boss system still like on at all no
it's not
different behavior from the other of the
pilot normal open pilot won't let me
engage in a stop
I was pressing resume
this car is much more of a joy to drive
than the set of guys I would really like
this to be the self-driving awareness to
our part to car I really like to be
taking this across the country but we're
gonna need a torque mud and we don't
need to rate our hack because you know
who needs a radar just use vision I was
the botanist I'm different
so the Bosch system has a crappy radar
that doesn't give you any objects
yes so this means open pilots can do
longitudinal control yeah
oh this is a Honda posture f
one of the only couple in existence
and thinking these in the program
using a comma power using the new common
power diode circuit very nice
yeah nitro I think is supported I think
at night actually works better than
during the
and it's even driving morganite I assume
uh-uh irises tractor
very nice maybe it's helpful we have the
line
guys no wobble there's a little wobble
in the Civic anymore right there come on
just don't have wobble
so you tell them on Sheldon about the
staring right yeah oh yeah almost lying
on their website about the sneering
Richmond so we have an optimizer now
that calculates the real car parameters
what's the press excited oh we can't
talk about the press yet it's under
embargo guys I don't get them all now
the press went very well Friday 6:00
a.m. guys can I uh how many spoke as you
got oh we've got 50 Scopus
who were depressed we definitely can't
talk about that does the fuse what's up
guys well the bar system tries to fuse
it doesn't do a good job
terrible job
ours usually gets it if you're going
went below 40
so now the good stuff starts around the
highway
well is it good
yes it's the same model
but new models are going to be a lot
more frequent soon
the suppressor impressed
no pun intended can't order the press
guys
well we thought we need more tour I
don't like that one more torque oh my
god I feel bad for all of you who don't
have torque mods plebs with no torque
mods
that's pretty good
is this the same torque as the Civic
where it feels like less
and I think we're just spoiled maybe
you know finalized on Amazon Amazon
Amazon guys having some fried house I'm
Franco by go buy go buy leave good
reviews to
if we get 10,000 five-star reviews will
release the tour fun
it was really good
therefore that
we shouldn't I mean when that happens we
shouldn't feel it
adjustable
nice track table
also does this car lose speed
distracted for too long I don't know
actually
ask me harder than they get my food on
us because we're not
this guy
car is a great engine guys I think we
can't cancel
well but that's ballsy cuz then we can't
break
I assume this well exceeds the door
comin I am maybe have 50
pretty nice good experience wow really
fifty changes a lot yeah I mean the
torque goes with the square of the speed
so
now the Priuses with Park Assist don't
have the different steering ratio we
still have that Siri they have a
different steering column but that's why
the actuators more shitty they not
actually confirmed yet they certainly
have different firmware
I guess it's also turbo lag
yeah that is turbo like you're right
who's in gear early
if you ever been pulled over a running
Oakland violent yeah
bitch Oh
they asked if - count so on
put it in sport not
same turbo action we can now you can see
the boost pressure on the dash
well that's a good point
oh we allow engagement in sport one yeah
conveniently tells me the speed limit is
I can open why let's see right now
wisely smog
when the model is so good the model
loves the fog
it's better than I do it's easier to
look at the screen outside
yeah guys please enable your front
camera record and upload
say that this actuator cuts out we
needed a foothold it's like it's
slightly more sensitive
let's not cut out there when I don't
Moreau
so let's turn driver monitoring off and
ditch the light see what was that why
did I lose to get you better there
Scopus can see everything many to say
any questions
they were asking who is running a
periscope it's the other member of the
control scene yeah did any of you
already like you don't have a lot doing
our time when I get my face out there
that's good is he sees the stick
yeah I mean those horns like bobble go
this is good as a civic we should have
gone far I wish it was our launch to
some just like better about ours
I feel like it's pulsing
not sure what that is but maybe it's
just a road maybe no I suppose gentle
you know that adaptive cruise missiles
are so so aggressive as well yeah I know
maybe people actually like that I think
they do I think people complain about
ours not being aggressive enough
Big Momma won't even try to wave her
over there
as we're building a big bottle it's not
gonna be in 0.5 the big ball is gonna be
amazing
open pilot used to have small model but
we're gonna make big model that's too
dark
to do this
Wow
people want more aggressive ACC jokes I
know
knock
it's like shorter following distance
it's just not going to happen
okay with some more aggressive booms and
aces when the I Alexis ACC is more
aggressively sanitary
and I'm okay with that
Oh Marlo that's like left language
brassiere
I do like that a CC on the Cadillac for
you if you turn on the blinkers will
accelerate that's pretty nice
interests
what is big model they call
we used to have small model
it's gonna really push your yawns to the
limit
it needs more torque
and the Civic agency I forget to the
same excel as I probably do it I mean
the interface is a bit janky but
probably worker out there do we know
what the interface is on this I know I
forgot
it's too close too close
this big mobile talk are no talk are you
a poet car no rav4 is gonna get talked
about that as you're a floor is gonna
get short car the opposite of talking
see why is it still saying turn acute
steering even after I step on the gas
it did that before - you learned this
thing on the alert estanque on after he
step on the gas which I don't really
like is that designer
I'm
Carter's
let's really by design because the folks
can last for a really short time you
still want to show the alert yeah but
not if the user has canceled the system
yeah
the scope is have more questions
how'd you like to write
good right alright this would be a great
car passed by so much torque
imagine when consumers will start buying
cars based on actuator models exactly
Steff torque no lag yeah the Toyota has
way more torque than the Honda the
problem with the Toyota is it as lag so
you either get dangerous
this is the v6 model
caution steel plates say some of what's
in 0.5 under embargo
some secret stuff really think so I mean
there's one big thing that's secret but
it's not in 0.5 there's a big thing that
we showed to the press that's a secret
and it was not pandas on Amazon it was
not their boy class he never knows
shipped our brief is it
well the press had a nice - your friend
stuff oh well maybe that one was a
secret what's that a secret yeah well
it's not a secret anymore I did say I
told viv don't say the G word yeah the
press sir the press had a little bit of
G of X we wanted them to have a good
time not a bad move we turn it off we
did we were turned off for a few - a few
of the press outlets that we liked
actually I turned it off for all the
press outlets but I want them to think
that we liked the ball
or the 60fps you I said all the 60fps
you are
yeah the UI yeah I didn't leave words
we've been to him yeah after I've
disengage the alert should go I don't
know I just never see that alert
oh yeah there's some cool stuff in in
your UI
we have new you is 60fps we get that
butter smooth we also did a ton of work
across the system to lower CPU usage
uses way less CPU
yeah we're down to we're down to using
or using 60% of CPU now you ask
something like that everyone we're down
from like 80 to 60
they're close to the curb
I'm checking
cool scobie's that was a drive in the
Honda court with open piled 0.5 it's
coming out to de val 6:00 a.m. Friday
and keep an eye out for some coming at
press and guys if you want to buy more
yawns I'll buy them now we don't have
that many more left and there's a good
chance that the people will want to buy
them all and also if you're in slack or
get ready for the eternal September and
if you don't know what the eternal
September is